

Steve WEIDIG

Junior Web Developer

How to reach me:

Home:

+352 399 634

Mobile:

+352 621 758 846

Email

steve_weidig@yahoo.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/steve-weidig/

Portfolio:

https://github.com/Bofferbrauer

Address:

8, Rue des Genêts L-8447 Steinfort

Driving license and own car

Language Skills

Luxembourgish: Native speaker C2

French: Proficient C1 German Proficient C1 English: Proficient C1 Filipino: Beginner A2 Russian: Beginner A2 Spanish: Beginner A1

Personal Profile

I am a creative and flexible junior web developer with robust problem-solving skills and a high willingness to learn and teach new things. I gained many varied experiences in the past from previous jobs, which makes me very versatile.

Soft Skills

Creative, flexible, passionate to learn and try new things and to teach these to someone else, good problem-solving skills, able to work just as well alone as being part of a team, always willing to help colleagues, and team members, great communication skills, well organized and a high attention to details.

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, SQL, Python, YAML, RAML

Frameworks/Systems:

jQuery, Vue.js, Angular, React, React Native, Bootstrap, AJAX, NodeJS, Visual Studio Code, MySQL, PostgreSQL, XMAPP, Wordpress, Ionic, Anypoint Studio

Educational Training

Formation API Developer

- Enrolled from June 2022 to July 2022
- API Development and Deployment with Python
- PostgreSQL, Postman
- Git, GitLab

Brainnest Frontend Development Industry Training Program

- April 2022 to June 2022
- HTML, CSS and Javascript

API development trainee at Cap4Lab

- August 2021 to September 2021
- API development, creation and organisation

NumericALL CodingJobs

- Enrolled from February 2021 to May 2021
- Complete Front-end and Back-end training over 490 hours
- Numeral Frameworks like
 Vue.js, Angular and Bootstrap
- LAMPstack and JAMstack

NumericALL MyCompass

- Enrolled from December 2020 to January 2021
- Introduction into the different Jobs around Web development
- SEO, SEA, UX/UI
- Adobe XD, Wordpress

Career Summary

Translator FR-EN-DE

Freelance January 2018 to September 2020

- Transcription of movies and TV series
- · Translation of Websites
- Article writing
- Light copywriting

Multipurpose Worker

Commune de Sanem February. 2016 to December 2017

- Gardening
- · Park maintenance
- Distribution

Secretary-Receptionist

Publicité Benoy July 2012 to August 2013

- Drafting, writing and mailing contracts
- Planning and executing the schedule of the workers
- · Filing and archiving documents

Security Agent

Group 4 Securicor (G4S) June 2007 to June 2012

- Ensuring the protection of persons and facilities
- Fire safety tests
- Reception, sorting and distribution of internal company mail

Brewer and Malter

Brasserie Nationale Bofferding September 2003 to September 2006

- Drink production
- Quality control
- Automation
- · Depot management

Development Homeschooling

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2022 & Complete Web And Mobile Designer 2022

Courses on Udemy

- Enrolled since January 2021
- Complete courses for both Front-end and Back-end
- Designing Websites, from a sketch to the final product.
- MongoDB and NoSQL
- UX/UI, typography, Gestalt
- Figma, Canva

Education

Security agent trainee

CNFPC

February 2007 to June 2007

- SSIAP 1 (Service Sécurité Incendie et Assistance à Personnes)
- First Aid
- Guiding first respondents

Brewer trainee

Fritz-Henßler Berufskolleg (Germany) 2004 to 2006

Chemistry

Lycée Technique du Centre 1998 to 2002

Hobbies and points of interest

Videogames, PC hardware, programming, cycling, long walks, movies, chemistry, rocketry, space exploration